[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9501_Grace_s01_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_01_CROW_GracelessRequest_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "95_s01_01_Bag",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "Title": "The Silver Crows",
        "Description": "Grace O'Malley has developed a plan to found an enterprising new group of heroes who can work together to face the threats of Aeternum and possibly earn a little coin in the process.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Give up on escaping Aeternum?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Grace O'Malley never gives up! I just changed my mind. It's not so bad on Aeternum, long as there's good company and good coin. \\n\\nSo I'm thinking we build on your reputation and start a heroes for hire sort of affair.",
        "InProgressResponse": "These pesky Corrupted keep turning up everywhere. \\n\\nI'm starting to get used to it.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Now we got a safe place for the Silver Crows to call home! It's time to start expanding the crew and earning some coin! \\n\\nI'd swear I've crossed this entire island ten times now, so I'll handle this place - you do the footwork.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9501_Grace_s01_04",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_03_CROW_BestOfAeternum_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "Title": "The Best of Aeternum",
        "Description": "The Silver Crows need more members. Work with Grace to find additional heroes to join the group.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I can help with recruiting too.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Well now, that'd be most welcome, posting flyers and conducting these interviews could be a team effort. \\n\\nI've been poking around different settlements, I think Mourningdale's the best place to recruit.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I can tell you don't like the idea of finding true talent by posting notices. \\n\\nBut you'll see, it's a mercenary company tradition.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Clearly, that was not the best of Aeternum. \\n\\nI could tell you didn't like this idea to begin with, and you were right. We need another way.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9502_Zander_s01_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_04",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_03",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_04_CROW_ZanderTheRed_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "95_s01_05_2hWarhammer",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "Title": "Zander the Undying",
        "Description": "Grace has a great candidate in mind. Locate Zander the Undying and convince him to join the Crows.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Impressive. Where's Zander now?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Word is, he's left his old employer, a bit of a shady outfit, but that might not be so terrible. \\n\\nZander's hunkered down in a small cabin over in Edengrove. He's expecting you, so go talk to him and then you make the call.",
        "InProgressResponse": "This Zander character seems like he'd round out our team pretty well. \\n\\nLet me know what you think.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Thank you, my friend. This is very clever, making a treat to heal the kitty-cat. \\n\\nI must think about this some more. Perhaps I can create a new recipe or two of my own for the little fellow.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin",
        "Type": "SeasonQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9501_Grace_s01_05",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_05",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "95_s01_04",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_05_CROW_CanonAndCoin_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "DarkMatter",
        "ItemRewardQty": 40,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "Title": "Canon and Coin",
        "Description": "Help Zander find a way out of his organization.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What happened to him?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "You are speaking to him. After she released me, she said I could take time away, but leaving would never be an option. \\n\\nMaybe you can change her mind? It's up to you, but without her approval, I'm stuck.",
        "InProgressResponse": "If you talk to Granny, beâ€¦ diplomatic. \\n\\nI can still hear the sound of dirt hitting the lid of that coffin.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "First off, great work getting Zander to sign on, he'll be a great add to our team. \\n\\nSecond, that mangy dog he brought? It has to go.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9504_Shailyn_S01_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "95_s01_X1",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_X1_EXPD_Empyrean_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "95_s01_e03_2hGreatAxe",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Repeatable": null,
        "Title": "The Empyrean Forge (Expedition)",
        "Description": "Shailyn wants to uncover what Loth and his Varangians are doing in the Forge. Help her find Loth.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Why would you want that?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Because he has given in to madness and savagery, joined with the Varangians. \\n\\nSer Loth is who I speak of, and within the Empyrean Forge, his forces seek to claim a power that could be the unmaking of us all.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I await news of your success, young one.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I watched from afar and saw Ser Loth's Varangian allies in quite a disarray. Whatever you accomplished in there - it must've worked. \\n\\nTell me, though, had any of them acquired the full power of the Forge?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 60,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9517_OtmarWinkler_s01_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 60,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "95_s01_X2_EXPD_EmpyreanRepeat_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "GypsumOrb",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Repeatable": true,
        "Title": "A Toymaker's Request (Expedition)",
        "Description": "Otmar is interested in collecting rare Apatite Gems to make runeglass to make his \"toys.\" Help him find the gems in the Empyrean Forge.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I might.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Such providence! I am interested in obtaining Apatite Gems only found in the Forge. \\n\\nYou see, I use them to construct runeglass containers which can highly enhance the conductivity-- Ja, well, in short, to make my toys.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Did you know, I originally tried to run a sweets shop. Winkler's Aeternal Sweetmeats. \\n\\nMy favorite was the candied Spriggan liver. Ah, but my customers only cared for the toys.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Wonderful, you found the gems! Oh, you are-- well, a wonder! \\n\\nWith this, I can create at least two more Corrupted Ogre golems. And yes, yes, the eyes light up red, of course!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": "",
        "ScheduleId": "Daily"
    }
]
